An introduction to integration management.
So if you look at your process map,
which is page 25 of your PIMBAC,
this is that top row going across, which
means it will cover
our five process groups.
So this is the focus of the PM on the
traditional predictive projects.
So this is a master knowledge area.
This is everything we focus on because we
need to manage, coordinate, unify that
entire project to take it from beginning
to end.
All right.
So if we look at your slides, this is a
master knowledge area.
It will include all the other knowledge
areas.
So everything happening below will roll up
to us in integration.
So if we're going across the row in
initiation, This is where your project or
phase is initiated, started, and the phase
defined.
Then we'll move over into planning once
we've gone through initiating processes.
This is where we'll formulate
our project management
plan and all the pieces
called subsidiary plans.
We'll move into executing to direct and
manager project work.
That's when the work of the project will
be done according to the plan.
and we'll immediately be monitoring and
controlling, reviewing tracking against
the plan, progress, to see if there's any
variance.
If there is, that's why
you'll see the process
right below it is perform
integrated change control.
That is where change control will be
performed once our project is baseline.
And when we move over to the last process
group within the
integration, knowledge area.
We close the project or phase.
If you have a phased project, so close the
project or phase.
If you have a phase that is ending,
like in a construction project,
you have the design phase.
We have the designs completed.
Our deliverables are done for that phase.
We will continue to
the next phase, as long
as the stakeholders
want to continue doing so.
And then we'll go through our five process
groups again until we finally close,
complete the entire project.
We'll go through all the specifics in the
upcoming slides and lessons.